{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239229439","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239229439"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" ae2a9c74-f419-43e8-a560-45efb859494a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239229662","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239229662"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" ae2a9c74-f419-43e8-a560-45efb859494a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239230626","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239230626"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" ae2a9c74-f419-43e8-a560-45efb859494a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239231901","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239231901"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" ae2a9c74-f419-43e8-a560-45efb859494a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239234774","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239234774"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" ae2a9c74-f419-43e8-a560-45efb859494a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239235618","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239235618"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" ae2a9c74-f419-43e8-a560-45efb859494a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239235931","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239235930"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" ae2a9c74-f419-43e8-a560-45efb859494a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239237166","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239237166"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" ae2a9c74-f419-43e8-a560-45efb859494a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239240653","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239240653"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" ae2a9c74-f419-43e8-a560-45efb859494a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239241637","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239241637"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" ae2a9c74-f419-43e8-a560-45efb859494a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239241891","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239241891"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" ae2a9c74-f419-43e8-a560-45efb859494a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239242835","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239242835"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" ae2a9c74-f419-43e8-a560-45efb859494a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239245670","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239245670"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" ae2a9c74-f419-43e8-a560-45efb859494a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239246704","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239246704"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" ae2a9c74-f419-43e8-a560-45efb859494a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239247178","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239247178"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" ae2a9c74-f419-43e8-a560-45efb859494a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239251707","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239251707"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" ae2a9c74-f419-43e8-a560-45efb859494a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239251827","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239251827"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" ae2a9c74-f419-43e8-a560-45efb859494a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239279251","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239279250"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239283327","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239283327"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239286883","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239286883"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239291631","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239291631"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239298664","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239298664"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239302457","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239302457"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239305692","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239305691"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239309117","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239309117"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239312289","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239312289"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239317476","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239317475"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239324308","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239324308"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239327765","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239327765"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239330912","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239330912"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239335706","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239335706"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239341604","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239341604"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239345069","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239345069"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239352240","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239352240"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239355907","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239355907"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239365179","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239365179"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239369870","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239369870"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239376554","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239376553"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239380601","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239380601"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239385811","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239385811"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239389338","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239389338"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239392439","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239392439"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239396498","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239396498"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239399951","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239399951"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239404301","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239404301"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239410065","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239410064"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 2018942a-cf01-4b07-90b4-c959a948480b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239424057","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239424057"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 5fb6944c-6cd6-4c79-9795-23f2f8b67aec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239429342","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239429342"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 5fb6944c-6cd6-4c79-9795-23f2f8b67aec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239434295","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239434295"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 5fb6944c-6cd6-4c79-9795-23f2f8b67aec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239439954","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239439954"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 5fb6944c-6cd6-4c79-9795-23f2f8b67aec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239445206","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239445206"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 5fb6944c-6cd6-4c79-9795-23f2f8b67aec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239449615","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239449615"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 5fb6944c-6cd6-4c79-9795-23f2f8b67aec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239454815","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239454815"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 5fb6944c-6cd6-4c79-9795-23f2f8b67aec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239459135","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239459135"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 5fb6944c-6cd6-4c79-9795-23f2f8b67aec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239465681","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239465680"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 5fb6944c-6cd6-4c79-9795-23f2f8b67aec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239472209","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239472209"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 5fb6944c-6cd6-4c79-9795-23f2f8b67aec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239475463","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239475463"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 5fb6944c-6cd6-4c79-9795-23f2f8b67aec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239485314","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239485314"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 6688068f-b16f-4494-b593-b1de8ba5d651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LALA"," userResponse":" LALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239490081","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239490081"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 6688068f-b16f-4494-b593-b1de8ba5d651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239491643","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239491642"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 6688068f-b16f-4494-b593-b1de8ba5d651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lamba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAMBA"," userResponse":" LAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239496441","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239496440"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 6688068f-b16f-4494-b593-b1de8ba5d651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lamba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239498013","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239498012"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 6688068f-b16f-4494-b593-b1de8ba5d651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239503077","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239503077"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 6688068f-b16f-4494-b593-b1de8ba5d651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239503997","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239503997"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 6688068f-b16f-4494-b593-b1de8ba5d651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" laini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAINI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239504684","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239504684"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 6688068f-b16f-4494-b593-b1de8ba5d651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" laini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAINI"," userResponse":" LAINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239519703","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239519703"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 6688068f-b16f-4494-b593-b1de8ba5d651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" laini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239519840","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239519840"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 6688068f-b16f-4494-b593-b1de8ba5d651"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" laini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAINI"," userResponse":" LAINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239531360","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239531358"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LALA"," userResponse":" LALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239535349","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239535349"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239536953","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239536953"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lamba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAMBA"," userResponse":" LAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239539940","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239539940"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lamba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAMBA"," userResponse":" LAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239541544","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239541544"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239546512","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239546512"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239548111","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239548111"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" laini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAINI"," userResponse":" LAINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239551649","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239551649"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" laini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAINI"," userResponse":" LAINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239553255","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239553255"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMA"," userResponse":" LIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239555853","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239555852"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMA"," userResponse":" LIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239557431","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239557430"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" limau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMAU"," userResponse":" LIMAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239566451","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239566451"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" limau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMAU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239568490","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239568490"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" limau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239568732","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239568732"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" limau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMAU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239574409","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239574408"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" limau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239582326","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239582326"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" limau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239592062","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239592062"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" limau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239598398","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239598398"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" limau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239606527","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239606527"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 0370e943-534f-4eb3-aa89-fce9e2d979cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" limau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239632897","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239632896"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 6374b0a6-76ca-4c23-89ae-1c124d14415f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_w_l"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239639622","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239639622"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 6374b0a6-76ca-4c23-89ae-1c124d14415f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_o_ch"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239647233","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239647233"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 6374b0a6-76ca-4c23-89ae-1c124d14415f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_o_ch"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239653893","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239653893"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 6374b0a6-76ca-4c23-89ae-1c124d14415f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_l_u"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239658007","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239658007"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 6374b0a6-76ca-4c23-89ae-1c124d14415f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_o_l_u"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239664085","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239664084"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 6374b0a6-76ca-4c23-89ae-1c124d14415f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_o_l_u"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239671414","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239671414"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 6374b0a6-76ca-4c23-89ae-1c124d14415f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_o_l_u"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239678157","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239678157"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 6374b0a6-76ca-4c23-89ae-1c124d14415f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_o_l_u"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239695404","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239695404"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 84d13960-788c-4e70-b1f7-b792f631ba8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239696440","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239696440"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 84d13960-788c-4e70-b1f7-b792f631ba8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239698078","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239698078"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 84d13960-788c-4e70-b1f7-b792f631ba8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239698182","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239698182"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 84d13960-788c-4e70-b1f7-b792f631ba8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239709797","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239709797"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 84d13960-788c-4e70-b1f7-b792f631ba8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239716669","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239716668"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 84d13960-788c-4e70-b1f7-b792f631ba8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239722603","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239722603"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" 84d13960-788c-4e70-b1f7-b792f631ba8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239731824","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239731824"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" e4eaec57-e02d-4230-8340-8380836357b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_e-m-g"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239735262","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239735262"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" e4eaec57-e02d-4230-8340-8380836357b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-v-l"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239740084","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239740084"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" e4eaec57-e02d-4230-8340-8380836357b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_a-m-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239743802","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239743802"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" e4eaec57-e02d-4230-8340-8380836357b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_z-e-m"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239747003","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239747003"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" e4eaec57-e02d-4230-8340-8380836357b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-r-d"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239750646","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239750645"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" e4eaec57-e02d-4230-8340-8380836357b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_l-m-h"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239754224","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239754223"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" e4eaec57-e02d-4230-8340-8380836357b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_y-m-h"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239758110","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239758110"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" e4eaec57-e02d-4230-8340-8380836357b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_j-a-m"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239761666","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239761666"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" e4eaec57-e02d-4230-8340-8380836357b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_y-k-m"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239765208","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239765208"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" e4eaec57-e02d-4230-8340-8380836357b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_n-m-l"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239776031","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239776030"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" e4eaec57-e02d-4230-8340-8380836357b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_n-m-l"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239778917","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239778917"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" e4eaec57-e02d-4230-8340-8380836357b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_m_n-m-l"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239803416","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239803416"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" e4eaec57-e02d-4230-8340-8380836357b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_m_n-m-l"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550239810938","data":{"timestamp":" 1550239810938"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_170017"," gameId":" e4eaec57-e02d-4230-8340-8380836357b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_m_n-m-l"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}